Guide to the Stephen Maxfield Parrish papers, 1901-2010.
Parrish, Stephen Maxfield papers, 1901-2010.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Stephen Maxfield Parrish papers, 1901-2010.
14/12/3591
Stephen Maxfield Parrish
15.6 cubic feet.
Printed Materials, Correspondence, Research Materials, Microfilm, Photographs
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes correspondence, book reviews, subject files, and course material relating to his study of William Wordsworth and his career at Cornell. Also, correspondence between Jared Curtis, Coordinating Editor, and Stephen M. Parrish concerning The Cornell Wordsworth series and The Cornell Yeats series, as well as correspondence from others involved in those editing projects.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor of English, Cornell University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes correspondence, book reviews, subject files, and course material relating to his study of William Wordsworth and his career at Cornell.
Also, correspondence between Jared Curtis, Coordinating Editor, and Stephen M. Parrish concerning The Cornell Wordsworth series and The Cornell Yeats series, as well as correspondence from others involved in those editing projects.
Photographs by James Butler of an event celebrating the completion of the Wordsworth series held at Kendal at Ithaca on March 29, 2008.
Correspondence with Sally Bushell relating to The Excursion,1999-2002 and Mark L. Reed with Parrish, and letters between other editors and scholars relating to the series. Includes additional correspondence between Reed and Curtis, James Averill, Stephen Gill, Carl Ketcham, and Robert Osborn.
Cassette tapes of the Wordsworth Summer Conferences, 1991: Jonathan Wordsworth on Wordsworthian Comedy and 1998: Stephen Parrish on The Earliest Wordsworth; "Richard Wordsworth Reads the Poetry," and Jonathan Wordsworth/Studs Terkel talk.
Correspondence, grant proposals, reviews, and other files from Ann Saddlemyer, one of the general editors, relating to The Cornell Yeats series. Includes 17 CDs of interim stages of editions from Jared Curtis.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Parrish, Stephen Maxfield.; Wordsworth, William, 1770-1850.; Freud, Sigmund; Yeats, William Butler (W.B.)
Subjects:
College teachers.; English literature--Study and teaching; Cornell University--Faculty.; Cornell University. English Dept.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CD-1594 through CD-1610 contains manuscript materials, including transcriptions and photographic reproductions of interim stages of editions from Jared Curtis - Cornell Yeats series
Access Restrictions:
Box 15 restricted until 2017, except with permission from Ann Saddlemyer.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Correspondence
Series II. Publications
Series III. Freud
Series IV. Manuscript Materials
Series V. Various Material
Series VI: Audio/visual media
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Samuel Guttman, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Freud Concordance, 1989-2000 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Wordsworth: Various Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Wordsworth: Various Correspondence, 1970-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Publishers, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Jean Blackall, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Declan Kiely, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Yeats: Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Yeats: Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Various Correspondence, 1983-1992 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Various Correspondence, 1996-1968 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Various Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Various Correspondence, 1977-2004 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Yeats: Correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "Excursion" Correspondence, 1986-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Yeats: Memos to Editors, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - "Excursion" Correspondence, 2002-2001 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Yeats: British Library, 1995-2001 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Yeats: Bornstein, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Yeats: Cave, Richard, 1996-2002 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Yeats: Curtis, Jared, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Yeats: Curtis, Jared, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Yeats: Curtis, Jared, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Yeats: Eliot, Maurice, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Yeats: Finneran, Richard, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Yeats: Finneran, Richard, 1989-2000 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Yeats: Garcia, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Yeats: Guiness, Selina, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Yeats: Clark, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Yeats: Gould, 1988-2002 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Yeats: Harper, 1994-2003 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Yeats: Kiely, Declan, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Yeats: Marcus, Philip, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Yeats: Mays, 1995-2001 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Yeats: O'Donnell, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Yeats: Parkin, 2001-2004 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Yeats: Pethica, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence: Frank Roberts, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Yeats: Rohan, Virginia, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Yeats: Rohan, Virginia, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Yeats: Saddlemyer, 2001-2003 (Box 15)
    Formerly in Box 1 Folder 41. Restricted until 2017, except with permission from Ann Saddlemyer.
  - Yeats: Saddlemyer, 1995-2001 (Box 15)
    Formerly in Box 1 Folder 42. Restricted until 2017, except with permission from Ann Saddlemyer.
  - Yeats: Stallworthy, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Yeats: Stony Brook, 1996-2000 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Yeats: Watt, A.P., 2003 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Yeats: Worth, Katherine, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Assessments: Memo to Marquette U., 1984 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Harvard Book: Editorial Correspondence, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Various Correspondence, 1959-1971 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cornell English Dept. Correspondence, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Yeats: Correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Yeats: Winnett, Steven, 1995-2001 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Yeats: Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Yeats: Correspondence, 1992-1998 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Yeats: Correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Yeats: Holdeman, David, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - English Dept. Correspondence, 1997-2001 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Rawlings, Hunter, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Various Correspondence, 2002-2004 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Yeats: Kishel, Joseph (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Yeats: Harper, George, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Yeats: Macmillan Publishers, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Wordsworth: Notes and Correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Wordsworth: Notes and Correspondence, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Yeats: "The Wild Swans at Coole" Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Yeats Correspondence, 2001-2004 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Carol Landon, 1959-1988 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Wordsworth: Robinson, 1985-1990 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Hartman, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Wordsworth: Butler/Green, 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Various Correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Jonathan Wordsworth, 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Robert Kirkpatrick, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Carl Ketcham, 1986-1989 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - University of Lancaster, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Harvester Press, 1976-1983 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Freud: Contracts & Permissions, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Yeats: Cornell Press, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Yeats: Cornell Press, 1996-2002 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Yeats: Cornell Press, 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence between Reed and Parrish regarding Wordsworth, 1966-1975 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Series, general/policy, 1973-1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence regarding Peter Bell, Prelude, Waggoner MSS, 1974-1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - JFW - Prelude, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Michael Jaye Correspondence, 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - W.J.B. Owen Correspondence, 1971-1977 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - MSS Correspondence, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Reed, Gill Correspondence, 1966-1971 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Reed, Finch Correspondence, 1964-1967 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Parrish, Stephen, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Parrish, Stephen, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence from various people, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from various people, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Wordsworth, 1987-1992 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Curtis, Jared, 1970-1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Curtis, Jared, 1984-1991 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Curtis, Jared, 1992-1995 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Cornell-Dove Cottage Agreement and Permissions, 1978-1988 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Averill, James - Evening Walk, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Stephen Gill, 1991-1993 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Ketcham, Carl H., 1974-1978 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Osborn, Robert - Borderers, 1970-1974 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Editorial correspondence – personal/professional, 1977-1988 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence – Parrish, 1997-2000 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence – A-C, 1982-2002 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence – E-W, 1991-2006 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Mary Fitzgerald, Words upon the Window Pane 1 of 2, 1998-2001 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Mary Fitzgerald, Words upon the Window Pane 2 of 2, 1998-2001 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Mark Reed correspondence and other editorial files, 1965-1998 (Box 21)
  - Mark Reed correspondence and other editorial files, ca. 1963-1983 (Box 22)
- Series II: Publications
  - By Parrish
    - Essays (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - PMLA ( Publications of the Modern Language Association of America), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - PMLA, 1958-59 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Wordsworth Circile, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - PMLA, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Unpublished Papers, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Review essays, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - By Other Authors - Annotated
    - Annotated Publications - Various Authors (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Annotated Publications - Various Authors (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Series III: Freud
  - Grant Application, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - German Concordance, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Front Matter, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Translation Problem, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Reviews, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Freud & Aristotle: The Dogmatism Quotient (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Various Material (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Reviews, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Various Articles (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Various Articles (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Concordance: Freud Letters, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Concordances: Early History, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Hopkins Concordance, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Concordances: Misc. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Concordances: Eliot, 1983-1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Concordances: Eliot (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Freud Paper: American Psychoanalysts Association (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Freud's Metaphors of the Mind (die Seele), 1989 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Journals, 1976, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Reports, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Various Material, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Series IV: Manuscript Materials
  - Yeats: Dreaming of the Bones Manuscript Materials (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Yeats: Dreaming of the Bones Transcriptions (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Yeats: Dreaming of the Bones Transcriptions (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Yeats: The Road to Calvary (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Yeats: The Only Jealousy of Emer - Harvard Text (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Texts: Emer & Fighting the Waves (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Yeats: Draft 6: Emer & Fighting the Waves, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Yeats: Draft 6: Emer & Fighting the Waves, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Yeats: Draft 6: Emer & Fighting the Waves, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Yeats: Boston College Transcriptions, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Yeats: Manuscript Materials (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Yeats: Reels, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Yeats: Manuscript Materials (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Yeats: Manuscript Materials (cont.) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Yeats: Manuscript Materials (cont.) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Yeats: Manuscript Materials (cont.) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Yeats: Diarmuid and Grania Manuscript Materials (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Yeats: Diarmuid and Grania Manuscript Materials (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Yeats: The Only Jealousy of Emer & Fighting the Waves Manuscript Materials (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Yeats: The Only Jealousy of Emer & Fighting the Waves Manuscript Materials (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Yeats: The Only Jealousy of Emer & Fighting the Waves Manuscript Materials (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Yeats: Emer & Fighting the Waves - Draft 6 Appendixes, Editorial Materials, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Yeats: Emer Manuscript Materials (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Yeats: Emer Manuscript Materials (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Yeats: Emer & Fighting the Waves - Census of Manuscripts (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Yeats: Emer & Fighting the Waves - Census of Manuscripts (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Yeats: Dreaming of the Bones Manuscript Materials (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Yeats: The Road to Calvary Manuscript Materials (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Yeats: Emer - Transcriptions and Photo Reproductions (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Yeats: Emer - Transcriptions and Photo Reproductions (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Yeats: Emer - Transcriptions and Photo Reproductions (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Yeats: Emer & Fighting the Waves Manuscript Materials (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Yeats: Manuscripts, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Yeats: Census of Manuscripts (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Yeats: Census of Manuscripts (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Yeats: The King's Threshold Manuscript Materials (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Yeats: The King's Threshold Transcriptions (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Yeats: The King's Threshold Transcriptions (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Yeats: The King's Threshold Transcriptions (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Yeats: The King's Threshold Transcriptions (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Yeats: The Hour-Glass Manuscript Materials (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Yeats: The Hour-Glass Manuscript Materials (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Yeats: The Hour-Glass Manuscript Materials (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Yeats: The Hour-Glass Manuscript Materials (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Yeats: The Wild Swans at Coole Manuscript Materials (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Yeats: The Wild Swans at Coole Photographs (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Yeats: The Wild Swans at Coole Photographs (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Yeats: The Wild Swans at Coole Transcriptions (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Yeats: The Wild Swans at Coole Transcriptions (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Wordsworth: Jackson Sonnets - Photograph Orders and Receipts (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Yeats: The Wild Swans at Coole Transcriptions (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Yeats: The Wild Swans at Coole Transcriptions (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Wordsworth: Ecclesiastical Sketches Manuscript Materials (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Wordsworth: Manuscript Materials, Transcriptions (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Wordsworth: Yarrow Revisited, Tour in Scotland (1833) Manuscript Materials (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Wordsworth: Memorials of a Tour in Italy Manuscript Materials (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Wordsworth: Sonnets Manuscript Materials (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Series V: Various Material
  - Yeats: Cornell Press Contracts, 1995-2004 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Yeats: Grant Extension, 2002-03 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Press: Summaries of Editions for January, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Yeats: Reviews, 1996-2000 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Yeats: Reviews (cont.), 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Yeats: Various Poems (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Misc. Papers, 1979-1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Yeats: Chapman - Dreaming of the Bones, Calvary, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica on Wordsworth, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Talks Delivered, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - "The Two Wordsworths" and Other Articles, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Reed: 13-Book Prelude, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Wordsworth Letters: Sotheby's Auction (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Coleridge's Dejection: An Ode, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Coleridge's Dejection: An Ode, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Wordsworth: Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Wordsworth: Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Wordsworth: An Early History, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Wordsworth: An Early History, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Wordsworth: An Early History, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Yeats: Early History, 1986-1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Yeats: Texas Conference, 1990-1992 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Yeats: Texas Conference, 1990-1992 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Humanities Research: Spring Applications, 1980-1984 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Humanities Research: Spring Applications (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Cornell Press - Various Material (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Modern Language Association of America Committee on Scholarly Editions: Current Inspections, 1992-1995 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) Grant Application, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Yeats: Miscellaneous, 1989-1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Yeats: Sligo, Dublin, & Monaco, 1986-1990 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Yeats: Editorial Principles (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Agreement Between Sidnell & Chapman - The Countess Cathleen, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Pethica: Last Poems (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Parkinson Photos (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - "The Mad Monk:" An Early Ode of Wordsworth's? (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Dove Cottage Trust, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Material for "The Ruined Cottage" and "The Pedlar, ed. James Butler, 1976-1979 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Wordsworth: NEH Grants, 1977-79 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Wordsworth Letters, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Material for: Wordsworth - "The Fourteen Book Prelude," ed. Owen (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Owen Material (cont.), 1975-1980 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - John Finch Papers, 1964-1967 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - MLA Committee on Scholarly Editions - Inspections, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - MLA Committee on Scholarly Editions - Inspections, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - "Wordsworth's Ministry of Fear" (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Wordsworth Talks (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Wordsworth Talks, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - "Versioning Wordsworth", 1993 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Wordsworth: Final Volumes (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Permissions: Winnett, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Yeats: Various Material (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Yeats: Final Volumes in Progress, 2005 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Wordsworth: Draft (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Betz Exhibit, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Wordsworth: Grasmere Talk, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - The Wordsworth Circle, 1997, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Wordsworth: Grasmere Talk, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - PMLA (Publications of the Modern Language Association of America), 1965 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Cornell English Dept. Material (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Royalties Statements (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Photographs (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Cornell Yeats: Miscellaneous Material (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Reviews (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Wordsworth: Miscellaneous Material (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Winnett: The Only Jealousy of Emer & Breaking the Waves (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Miscellaneous Articles (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Texts: Emer & Fighting the Waves (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Cornell Department of English Material, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Yeats: The King's Threshold - Contract With Cornell Press (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Yeats: The Towers, ed. Richard Finneran (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - "Becoming a Yeatsian", 2004 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - The Cornell Yeats Project: Various Material (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - "Becoming a Yeatsian" (cont.), 2004 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Cornell Press Newsletter, 2002, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Cornell Yeats: Reports and Original Budgets, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Cornell Yeats: Early Stage Proposal, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Cornell Yeats: Grant Application - History, 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Yeats: Newspaper Articles, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Yeats: Collected Poems (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Curtis, Wordsworth Index, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Cornell Wordsworth: Early History (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Hull Fund, 1980-1992 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Jaye's Wordsworth & Coleridge Materials sold to Dove Cottage, 1991-1993 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Dove Cottage Manuscript Catalogues (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - NEH Applications: Curtis, Robinson (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Wordsworth: Darlington, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Wordsworth and Coleridge Articles: Praises, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Wordsworth: Electronic Texts, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Wordsworth: Encyclopedia Britannica, 1989-1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Wordsworth: Hayden Article, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Wordsworth: Anthology of Reading Texts, 1980-1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Wordsworth: Landon / Curtis Early Poems, 1989-1994 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Wordsworth: Landon / Curtis Early Poems, 1988-1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - The Cornell Wordsworth, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - MLA (Modern Language Association of America) Committee on Editions: Inspections, 1977-1990 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - MLA (Modern Language Association of America) Committee on Editions: Inspections, 1977-1983 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Sandstills: Sally Bushell (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Excursion: Bushell, etc., 1981-2000 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Excursion Preface, 1996, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Butler's Version of Jaye's Intro (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Jaye's Original, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Jaye's Original, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Jaye's Original, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Jaye's Original, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Jaye's Original, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Jaye's Original: Introduction Overflow, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Jaye's Original: Introduction Overflow, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Wordsworth: Reed (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Review of Cornell Wordsworth Volumes, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Carol Landon, 1980-1988 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Reviews of Cornell Wordsworth Volumes, 1981-1987 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Wordsworth: Cornell Press, 1966-1994 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Wordsworth: General, 1993-1996 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - "Wordsworth & His Circle" / Cornell Library Journal, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Yeats: O'Donnell, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Fitzgerald: Words on Window-Pane, 1995-1998 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Yeats: Responsibilities - Printed Texts and Transcripts (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Responsibilites: Miscellaneous Material, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Responsibilities: Texts and Transcripts, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Responsibilities (cont.) (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Responsibilities: Correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Jackson: Front Matter, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Wordsworth: Jackson Sonnets, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Wordsworth: Jackson Sonnets, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Wordsworth: Jackson Sonnets, 1985-1989 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Wordsworth: Jackson Sonnets, 1986-1989 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Cornell Library Wordsworth Manuscripts (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Sally Bushell correspondence, 1999-2002 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Yeats: Grant Applications - Atlantic Philanthropies (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Yeats: Expenses (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Yeats: The Words on the Window-Pane (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Yeats: "Parnell's Funeral" and Other Poems, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Yeats: Various Correspondence, 2000-2002 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Yeats: Misc. Material (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Parnell's Funeral and Other Poems from A Full Moon in March - Manuscript Materials (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Parnell's Funeral and Other Poems from A Full Moon in March - Manuscript Materials (cont.) (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Parnell's Funeral and Other Poems from A Full Moon in March - Manuscript Materials (cont.) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Yeats: Various Correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Yeats's Deirdre, ed. Virginia Rohan - Manuscript Materials (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Yeats's Deirdre - Rohan Transcriptions (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - V. Rohan - "The Writing of W.B. Yeats's Deirdre: A Study of the Manuscripts" (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - V. Rohan - "The Writing of W.B. Yeats's Deirdre: A Study of the Manuscripts" (cont.) (Box 9, Folder 14)